♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
["Mr. Tailor" playing]
♪ Holding the scissors ♪
♪ One cut, and it's over ♪
[Ibyang] Am I really your child?
[Olga] You just got scolded!
You're sulking already?
[Karla] There, they're the ones
we're chasing.
And that suitcase?
It contains five million pesos,
which we need to get.
- [Ame, in English] I have a bright idea.
- [Karla] Where's your friend?
- Didn't you say you're with your friend?
- Sweetheart, you're the only one I love.
[Gavin] That's just my friend.
[in English] That's Gavin!
Who will you choose?
Your best friend or your girlfriend?
[Cathy, in English] What's going on here?
- [Boyet] You're causing trouble!
- [Cathy's mom] Stop it!
[in English] That's my daughter!
Let me go!
- [Cathy's mom, in English] Call security!
- [Gavin] Stay here.
[Karla] Gavin! Stop them!
[Kiko] Where's my money?
- Boss, I really brought the five million.
- Hands up!
- I'm a cop!
- [cop] We'll take you to the station.
You'll explain there!
Oh, no, Atoy, she's just like you.
[Emerson] Your sister is just as tough.
Why? Are they siblings?
[hushes]
[Ame] For the success
of Operation Suitcase!
- [all, in English] Cheers!
- [in English] Hey, cheers! Cheers, cheers!
- [in English] I have to go.
- Audrey, wait.
[Atoy on the phone] I still love you.
Audrey.
I really miss you and Tatoy, Sister Ame.
Hey, Ibyang, what happened?
What are the plans for the child?
Do what we agreed on.
That's your only job. Okay?
[Olga] Hello. Friend?
I thought of something
we could make money from.
PREVIOUSLY
This is big money.
[music ends]
[T-Bak] Oh, there.
- [Karla] Oh!
- [T-Bak] Oh, take it.
‪[grunts]
Hey. PJ texted me earlier.
He said Gavin and Jason want to join.
Oh, that's another bet! [smirks]
Gavin's coming?
Oh? Why are you affected?
Oh, nothing!
Come on. Time out first. My God.
- [light music playing]
- [inhales]
[T-Bak] Gosh!
[man] My turn.
- [T-Bak] Oh.
- Oh, they're already here.
Wow. He's big.
He's big, huh.
- [music fades]
- So big.
Why isn't Gavin here?
[in English] He's with Cathy.
What? Let's go. Let's ball!
- [PJ] Game on, game on.
- [Jason] Oh.
[light music playing]
[T-Bak] Hey.
Don't be sad
just because Gavin isn't here.
[T-Bak] Don't worry.
He and Cathy will break up soon.
Hey. You…
We're Team Karla! Oh!
Shut up.
Keep dreaming, Karla.
[T-Bak] Game! The big one's mine.
There, oh!
[suave theme music playing]
[motorcycle revving]
[sewing machine whirring]
[scratches]
[snipping]
[clicking]
[sewing machine clacking]
- [gun cocks]
- [gunshots]
[gunshots]
[clicking]
[snipping]
[music swells]
- [electronic blipping]
- [music fades]
[indistinct chattering]
One bag contains food.
The other contains clothes and a blanket.
Thank you very much.
I hope more people like you will help us.
[Cathy] You're welcome.
["In Nothing" instrumental music playing]
- Thank you. Thank you.
- Thank you.
Babe, are there more blankets there?
[in English] We might need more.
[in English] Babe?
♪ It's not that… ♪
[in English] Babe!
Gavin!
I've been calling you.
Why do you look spaced out?
Our companions might think
my boyfriend has no interest in helping.
I'll be embarrassed.
[in English] Sorry.
[pensive music playing]
Ma'am, this is expired.
Throw this away. It can't be used anymore.
Let me see.
Yes, it's expired.
But you know, they won't notice that.
Just cover it with a marker,
and let's just give it away.
But, ma'am--
These poor people,
they don't care if the food has mold.
Especially when they're hungry.
If they fail to read that it's expired,
then it's their fault.
What's important is we were able
to give a lot of items.
- [in English] Okay?
- Okay, ma'am.
[in English] No, it's not okay.
Gavin?
You know…
Bro, bro, dispose of that.
They might get sick.
They already lost their homes.
Don't add to their problems.
[in English] I can't believe
you'd do that, Cathy.
You would risk people's health,
just to look good on camera?
You're judging me too much.
If you were in my shoes,
what do you think you'd feel
if I did that?
[rousing music playing]
Ibyang!
Ibyang, get your bag!
[sneaky music playing]
Ibyang!
[music fades]
- Oh!
- [Charmi] Oh, hello.
- I'll take care of that.
- Oh.
She already went upstairs.
She's so excited to be back here.
Where's Olga?
Wasn't she supposed to bring Ibyang here?
Ah, well, Olga has work now.
She had an early call time,
so she asked me instead.
Actually, she wanted to bring
the child to work,
but I said not to bring the child.
She might get tired.
Their taping is far. It's in Tanay.
Taping?
What's she going to tape? Boxes?
[laughs] You're funny!
No. Olga is an actress.
Oh.
I knew it.
That's why she looked familiar.
I think I saw her in a TV series.
She was a patient there.
That's it. Abot-Kamay na Pangarap.
Yes, she was an extra there.
One of the extras who died.
[laughs]
Oh. Okay.
Her mom will pick her up.
I'll go ahead. I'm in a hurry.
[Charmi] All right. Mmm.
Ibyang, enjoy! I'll go ahead!
- Okay.
- I'll tell her. Okay.
Okay. Bye!
[sneaky music playing]
It's good.
- Hmm.
- Hey, Gavin!
Ice candy. Want some?
- Sure.
- Mmm.
[Putoy] Oh?
Just one? Take another!
For your girlfriend.
No, just one. It's okay. Thank you.
Did you see Karla?
Karla? Ah…
You know, she was looking for you earlier.
Didn't you see her?
And why are you looking for her?
Your girlfriend might get mad.
Because I want to talk to her about Cathy.
Oh!
["In Nothing" instrumental music playing]
Is that a lovers' quarrel?
[in English] Something like that.
[clears throat]
Are you okay, bro?
We're just here.
We'll support you.
What's your problem?
[in English] I just realized…
I don't really know Cathy yet.
I thought she was okay, but I was wrong.
[in English] She's not
who I thought she is.
It's your fault!
From the start,
you should've gone for Karla instead!
[Billy] Exactly!
Kind, but brave.
Beautiful, but fierce!
And most of all…
[both] Not fake!
Hmm, exactly!
["In Nothing" by Wickermoss
with Neth Macam playing]
- [man 1] Let's share.
- [man 2] Unbelievable!
- Mmm!
- [mellow music playing]
Sister Karla, I know it's you.
I've missed you.
How did you know it was me?
That's impossible.
Well, I told her you were coming.
So, Karla?
Can you help me deliver that?
Because Atoy just told me now
that something needs to be delivered.
And I'm not even finished yet
with the other thing he asked me to do.
Okay, Sister Ame.
Just don't let Brother Atoy know
that I was the one who delivered it, okay?
Yes. Oh, thank you so much, Karla.
I'll come too, Sister Karla.
So we can bond.
Come on. Please?
This little one!
Bring her along,
so I can finish what I need to do.
Then when you get back,
I'll treat you with pares.
[Ibyang] Pares.
But what if her mom looks for her?
She'll be picked up tonight.
Her mom's working in Tanay.
Oh, Ibyang,
how are you and your mom?
Is she nice to you?
Yes. Mama is kind.
She takes care of me.
But she scolded me right away.
Because I did something wrong.
What did you do?
[melancholic music playing]
Well, then…
I broke a lot of things.
I got scared because I thought
she didn't love me.
Hey. She loves you, I'm sure.
Not just because she scolded you,
she even looked for you.
You know, the fact that she came for you,
that's a sign she loves you.
Right?
[bright music playing]
[in English] Hi, Karla. Ibyang!
He suddenly came too.
[Ibyang chuckles]
- Maybe he loves you too! [giggling]
- Shh! Hey! He might hear you.
[Karla] Ibyang.
Where are you going? I'll take you.
- No.
- We have… We have a ride!
No need. Ibyang and I can do this.
We can do this, right?
I insist. Let's go.
Oh, let's go, Ibyang. Sit in the back.
[in English] Okay. [giggling]
I'll just put this here, okay?
[Ibyang] Yes.
[Gavin sighs]
[music fades]
You're coming with us. Are you sure?
Won't Cathy get mad at you?
Don't worry about that.
[in English] So, where are we going?
[bright music playing]
I can handle this.
[Karla] Brother Emerson,
I already delivered what Sister Ame
asked me to deliver.
We're on our way home.
[indistinct chattering]
Really?
Fine.
Hurry up, okay.
[pleasant music playing]
[Gavin] Let's just wait there.
Do you want snacks or coffee? My treat.
Can we have both?
- [in English] Sure.
- Hey, Ibyang, we're not like that.
Gavin, that was just a joke.
But it's up to you if you want
to take it seriously.
Wait a minute. Can I quickly pee?
Oh, wow!
[in English] Mamsh, I love this look!
[in English] It's like, you know,
giving very quiet luxury,
with arrogance and horns.
- [chuckles]
- [giggles]
Charmi.
Yes?
[in English] Can you please
call my manager?
[in English] And order me
a blueberry cheesecake without cheese.
- A blueberry cheesecake without--
- A blueberry cheesecake without cheese?!
[laughing]
What?! [laughs]
- Okay. I'll go with you.
- [sneaky music playing]
- We'll just follow to the coffee shop.
- Okay, fine.
[laughing]
Hey, let's get serious now.
Enough of that.
- Actor's in now.
- Hey, actor's in.
[deep breathing]
[indistinct]
That's my mom.
- What?
- That's my mom.
If this gig becomes successful,
we'll be loaded.
I'll check out my cart right away,
shopping time!
Buy everything you want!
A hundred thousand is nothing
compared to what we'll earn now.
[cackling]
Oh, come on. Let's go to the coffee shop.
- Let's go, hurry!
- One hundred thousand, come to mama!
[cackles]
Oh, oh. Sorry-- Sorry, sir.
- [Ibyang] Sorry, sir.
- [Karla] ibyang!
[Ibyang] That's my mom!
[tense music playing]
[Ibyang] Where's my mom?
- Huh?
- [Karla] Where?
She was just here earlier.
Where is she?
She's in Tanay, right?
Isn't that where her taping is?
[in English] Oh, I'm sorry
to keep you waiting.
- [in English] No problem.
- [in English] I'm sorry.
Oh!
- [in English] You may take your seat.
- [in English] Why, thank you, kind sir.
[sneaky music playing]
- [in English] Um, are you British?
- [clears throat]
[in English] Um, oh, no.
[in English] I'm from Caloocan.
[in English] Um,
I just travel there a lot.
[chuckles]
[in English] I love Europe.
[in English] Really?
- I also came from there last week.
- [Olga] Oh!
[in English] When was
the last time you went there?
[in English] Ah, where did you stay?
[chuckles]
- [phone ringing]
- [in English] Oh, excuse me.
- [in English] Oh, it's my daughter.
- Oh.
[Olga on the phone] Hi!
[in English] Oh, hello,
my beautiful daughter.
Mama, is that you?
[in English] Of course, my darling.
[chuckles]
[in English] I'm quite busy right now.
[in English] Oh, okay. I'll call you back.
[in English] Ta-ta!
[in English] "Ta-ta"?
Why does Mama talk like that?
Isn't she at a taping?
Maybe she's just in character.
[in English] I ordered for us.
- [music fades]
- [in English] Wow!
For you.
[in English] Wow.
[light music playing]
- Thank you, brother!
- Of course.
Oh no! I'm embarrassed.
You already came with us,
and now you're treating us to coffee.
It's fine.
Caramel macchiato for us.
[in English] For Ibyang, milk chocolate.
Ibyang, maybe you want something to eat?
Just tell me.
There are delicious pastries outside.
Check them out.
Really?
Of course.
You'll pay for it?
Of course. Just choose.
I'll take care of it.
[music fades]
Gavin, won't Cathy look for you?
Did you tell her you're coming with us?
[in English] I don't need to do that.
[in English] She's not my mom.
Did you fight?
Not really.
I just got tired of being with her.
Because I'm just her assistant
when she does volunteer work.
Or if not, just the videographer.
Gosh! If the videographer and assistant
were as handsome as you,
I'd be happy.
Let me see, let me see!
Oh!
[in English] That's my boy
from Barangay Tabang Lupa!
There, oh. Cute dimple, oh.
Stop teasing me.
Me, handsome?
No, ugly.
Do you like that?
[light music playing]
You know, love your face.
Because no one else made that,
except you and your mom.
[music fades]
[in English] Legit!
[light music playing]
You know, Karla, I like being with you.
[in English] Why I didn't see that before?
Why did you say that all of a sudden?
Because you're genuine.
[in English] I can be
my true self when I'm with you.
Why? With Cathy, not so?
To be honest, no.
Because even she isn't real.
I didn't realize right away
that she was just pretending.
[pensive music playing]
[in English] Why are you selling it?
What a waste.
[in English] No.
[in English] Not to me.
- [chuckles softly]
- [sneaky music playing]
Um, my ex left that after…
after he…
dumped me for another woman.
He wanted it back,
because it's limited edition.
[man] Oh.
[in English] But I don't care.
[in English] I just want my revenge.
[in English] Serves him right.
But maybe
you can give me a discount?
[in English] Maybe
you can drop the price to…
150k?
[in English] You want
to get rid of this, right?
[in English] Oh.
[music fades]
[in English] Excuse me.
[in English] I'm so sorry.
I can't help it, but…
Um, my husband
is a watch collector, and um…
it's our anniversary.
[in English] Sir, can I see that?
[in English] Ah, sure.
[Charmi, in English] Thank you.
[in English] Oh my God!
Is this it?
[in English] In the flesh!
[chuckles]
[gasps]
[in English] Oh my God!
[sneaky music playing]
This is one of the collections
my husband is looking for.
[in English] This is very rare!
Only four exist.
- [in English] Yes.
- Three are in museums.
[in English] Oh God!
[in English] Oh, love it! Oh.
- [chuckles]
- [Charmi] Oh, um…
Um, how much are you selling this for?
- [in English] Two hundred.
- [in English] Deal.
- [in English] Oh, s-sorry.
- Hmm?
[in English] It's already sold.
What? Really?
- You'll buy it? Two hundred?
- [man] Yes.
Can you afford it?
- [man] Mm-hmm.
- You're sure?
- [in English] Sure.
- Oh.
[Charmi] Too bad.
That would've been perfect for my husband.
[in English] Well,
you are a very lucky customer.
Very. Thank you!
[scoffs]
[in English] How much again?
[in English] Two hundred.
[mid-tempo rock music playing]
[Mercado, in English]
The laptop is locked and requires a code.
Aside from the ambassador,
the only person who knows the code
is the head of IT of the embassy.
She is Lily Santiago.
[mid-tempo rock music playing]
[Mercado] After your retrieval
at the embassy,
she went into hiding.
And according to our intel,
she is the goddaughter
of the mayor of San Lazaro City,
and there's a big possibility
she's hiding here.
Your mission is to get her,
not just to decode the laptop,
but to save her life
because there's a big possibility
the Zahran embassy
is also looking for her.
[in English] Good luck, Padua.
[music fades]
[gate hinge squeaks]
Thanks to the boss.
Chief, thank you.
[group member 1] We're leaving now.
The Mayor is so kind.
I am completely satisfied.
Let's go.
[gate hinge squeaks]
[music fades]
- Oh, sir.
- [Atoy] Sir.
Is the Mayor there? Can I talk to him?
Don't you have an appointment scheduled?
No, really.
Just go to the municipal hall
so someone can assist you.
I really want to talk to the Mayor.
Sorry, sir. We're strict right now
because the Mayor received a death threat.
[Atoy] Oh.
- Okay, sir.
- Okay, sir. Sorry.
[music swells]
[in English] Oh, I'll… I'll go ahead.
- [in English] Thank you.
- [man, in English] Thank you.
[in English] Thank you.
[chuckles]
[in English] Okay.
[in English] Bye. Enjoy!
[chuckles]
[sneaky music playing]
[in English] Oh my…
[in English] Oh, it's fake!
[in English] I got scammed!
[in English] Scammer!
[tense music playing]
[in English] Mama?
[man, in English] Stop her! Get that girl!
[in English] Get that girl! Scammer!
Sister Karla!
I saw Mama!
[in English] Are you sure?
Yes.
I thought she was
at the taping.
But Mama was just pretending!
Didn't Sister Ame say that Brother Atoy
and your mama know each other?
Maybe they just have the same job.
No.
It looked like Mama scammed the man.
That's why he chased her.
The man said, Scammer, scammer!"
[pensive music playing]
I hope Mama is okay.
[tense music playing]
Oh, brother, hurry up!
Well…
Gosh, I told you,
run after her immediately!
- My God, she's a scammer!
- We're looking for her, sir.
Where is she? You're too slow.
We should've caught her already.
She's a thief!
- Nothing, sir.
- Oh no.
[sighs]
You're too slow! You need to find her.
- [man] If she gets away, that's it!
- [guard] Sir, just report it
- to the office, sir.
- [man] That will take too long!
[guard] It will be resolved, sir.
- [man] Oh, no. Jeez.
- [guard] Just file a report.
Jeez.
[thumps]
[romantic music playing]
[thuds]
Are you okay?
Ah, because me, I'm fine.
Even if you stay here forever, my love.
- What do you mean, "My love"?!
- [quirky sting]
Ouch, ouch.
- Come on.
- Where is it?
[sneaky music playing]
[Olga] Oh my God!
[Olga pants]
[in English] Oh. Ah, may I?
[Emerson] Ah.
Mmm.
[pleasant music playing]
[in English] Perfect fit, ah.
Like a fairytale.
- [chuckles]
- Of course, it's perfect!
That's my shoe!
[grunts and groans]
- [thumps]
- [Olga, in English] Fool!
- I'm just helping you.
- [guard] There's someone there.
[Olga] I'm out of here!
[man, in English]
Maybe it's her! Stop her!
[Emerson, in English] My love!
[tense music playing]
Wait. My love!
- [music fades]
- [electronic blipping]
[tense music playing]
Oh? Are you okay? Did you get hurt?
The watch was immediately exposed as fake.
I haven't even left yet.
What's important is you
and the money are safe.
I thought I could escape.
UP NEXT
[Olga] That fool bumped into me.
That was you.
You just don't have your mole, but…
I can't be mistaken.
[dramatic sting]
Liar!
I'm your mother. You're my daughter!
What do you want me to do
so you'll believe me, Ibyang?
What are you saying?
I'm not a member of the syndicate.
You're even doubting
your family now.
You're too paranoid.
[in English] Oh my God.
[in English] Our intel told us
that the decoder of this town
is the mayor's niece.
[in English] So, she might be here.
[Samir, in English] He might be here too.
[in English] This man has many faces.
["Mamang Sastre" playing]
♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
♪ Holding the scissors ♪
♪ One cut, and it's over ♪
♪ Fix it ♪
Subtitle translation by: Rachel C. Arias